<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Toru Niina</title><link>https://toruniina.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Toru Niina</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>niina.toru.68u@gmail.com (Toru NIINA)</managingEditor><webMaster>niina.toru.68u@gmail.com (Toru NIINA)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 18:39:24 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://toruniina.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Biography</title><link>https://toruniina.github.io/biography/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 18:28:40 +0900</pubDate><author>niina.toru.68u@gmail.com (Toru NIINA)</author><guid>https://toruniina.github.io/biography/</guid><description>Affiliation Takada Lab. Dept. Biophysics, Div. Biol. Graduate School of Science Kyoto University, Japan
Interests Biophysics Computer Simulations Software Engineering (C++, Rust) Technical Skills C++ 98/11/14/17 Rust 2015/2018 C 99 Fortran 90/95 CUDA Python 3 Linux Server maintainance Publications See Publications.
Educational/Work history 2019/04/01~ JSPS Research Fellowship for Young Scientists DC2 2018/04/01~ RIKEN Center for Biological Dynamical Research (BDR), Laboratory for Biologically Inspired Computing, Research Part-time Worker.</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>https://toruniina.github.io/publications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 18:28:40 +0900</pubDate><author>niina.toru.68u@gmail.com (Toru NIINA)</author><guid>https://toruniina.github.io/publications/</guid><description>Publications Research Articles Molecular dynamics simulation of proton-transfer coupled rotations in ATP synthase FO motor Shintaroh Kubo†, Toru Niina†, and Shoji Takada († equal contribution). Scientific Reports (in press). bioRxiv: https://doi.org/10.1101/618504 Flexible Fitting of Biomolecular Structures to Atomic Force Microscopy Images via Biased Molecular Simulations Toru Niina, Sotaro Fuchigami, and Shoji Takada. JCTC (2020). bioRxiv: https://doi.org/10.1101/793901 Sequence-dependent nucleosome sliding in rotation-coupled and uncoupled modes revealed by molecular simulations Toru Niina†, Giovanni B.</description></item><item><title>Building a website powered by Hugo and LoveIt</title><link>https://toruniina.github.io/posts/building-a-website-powered-by-hugo-and-loveit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 20:28:40 +0900</pubDate><author>niina.toru.68u@gmail.com (Toru NIINA)</author><guid>https://toruniina.github.io/posts/building-a-website-powered-by-hugo-and-loveit/</guid><description>Installing Hugo and LoveIt Follow the official documentation. Note that required version of Hugo is relatively high.
https://gohugo.io/getting-started https://themes.gohugo.io//theme/LoveIt/theme-documentation-basics/ Changing Fonts While Unicode defines CJK Unified Ideographs, actually, the forms of Japanese Kanji are slightly different from those of the Chinese characters. So we need to change fonts to render Japanese Kanji in a proper way.
We can override the variables defined in LoveIt via config/css/_override.scss. By overriding global-font-family, we can use fonts for Japanese letters.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://toruniina.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 18:39:24 +0900</pubDate><author>niina.toru.68u@gmail.com (Toru NIINA)</author><guid>https://toruniina.github.io/projects/</guid><description>Software Projects See the list of repositories also.
Mjolnir Watch Star Fork general purpose coarse-grained molecular dynamics simulation package
language: C++11 + OpenMP
Mjolnir is a molecular dynamics simulation software focusing on coarse-grained simulation.
I am the original designer, implementer and owner of the project.
toml11 Watch Star Fork TOML for Modern C++
language: C++11, 14, 17
toml11 is a library to handle TOML file in a C++ code.</description></item></channel></rss>